<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Catdogwalrus</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_chapter_menu">ChapterMenu</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="text_fragment">Lesson text fragment</string>
    <string name="code_fragment">Source code fragment</string>
    <string name="next_button">Next</string>
    <string name="back_button">Back</string>

    <!-- Strings for Lesson 1.1 -->
    <string name="lesson1_1_1">
        First part of the lesson.
    </string>
    <string name="lesson1_1_2">
        After next button is pressed.
    </string>
    <string name="lesson1_1_3">
        Last slide, game should be next
    </string>

    <!-- Strings for code, Lesson 1.1 -->

    <string name="high_score">catdogwalrushighscore</string>
    <string name="Hello_world_test">
    #include &#60;iostream&#62; \n\n
    int main()\n
    {\n
	    std::cout &#60;&#60; "Hello World!&#92;n";\n
	    return 0;\n
    }
    </string>

    // Each code segment is surrounded by @ symbols. Load these into arrays. Periods, ?, !, indicate the end of a lesson segment.
    <string name="lesson1_text">


Let’s talk about variables.If you have ever taken a math class you have probably seen variables of some kind. Equations for example are made up of variables, letters that represent numbers you pick.$

In programming you have variables just like this but instead of the variables only being used for numbers you can use them to represent almost anything!


Int
Double
Char
String
Bool

Int is used to represent an integer, which is a whole number.

@
int a, b;\n
int c = 15;
@

Double is used when you want to represent a decimal value.

@
int a, b;\n
int c = 15;\n
double d = 10.2;
@

Char is used to represent a single character. This can be a letter or symbol from the keyboard. You use single quotes around the character to show it is a single character.

@
int a, b;
int c = 15;
double d = 10.2;
char e = ‘e’;
@

Next we talk about string. String is how we show a series of characters that are connected.$ This is basically a strange way of saying a sentence. You can type inside of double quotes to indicate it is a string.

@
int a, b;
int c = 15;
double d = 10.2;
char e = ‘E’;
string f = “This string is cool!!! ”;
@

Finally, the last major type we have is a bool. This is short for the word boolean. This type of value holds either true or false.

@
int a;
int c = 15;
double d = 10.2;
char e = ‘E’;
string f = “This string is cool!!! ”;
bool g = true;
@

Think you can match the data with the type of variable you need? Lets go!

    </string>

</resources>
